http://www.buccaneers.com/team/privacy-policy

Posted: July 2020
This privacy policy applies to Buccaneers Team LLC website www.buccaneers.com, our mobile application, online shop https://shop.buccaneers.com, and any online services that link to this policy (collectively, the "Services"). The purpose of this privacy policy is to disclose to you what information we may collect, how we may collect it, with whom we may share it, and certain other matters related to such information, including the choices you have regarding our collection of information and our use and disclosure to other parties of information we may have collected from you.
The Services are operated by Buccaneers Team LLC.
If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please contact legal@buccaneers.nfl.com. If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S. based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request.
When this privacy policy uses the term "personal information," we mean information that identifies a particular individual. When other information, such as a favorite team or player, is associated with personal information, it also becomes personal information for the purposes of this privacy policy.
Please read the information below to learn more about our data collection policies and practices.
1.     Types Of Information That May Be Collected
2.     How Information May Be Collected
3.     How We Use The Information Collected
4.     With Whom The Information May Be Shared
5.     Security
6.     Chat Rooms, Forums, And Message Boards
7.     Links To Other Websites
8.     A Special Note For Parents Concerning Privacy
9.     Notification Of Changes And Your Acceptance Of The Privacy Policy
10.  Personal Information Access and Correction
11.  California Consumer Privacy Act Disclosure
12.  Questions About This Privacy Policy
TYPES OF INFORMATION THAT MAY BE COLLECTED
The following are the types of information we may collect:
Information You Provide Us: In the course of using the Services, we may ask you to provide us with certain information, including without limitation, contact information (such as your name, mailing address, email address or phone number), demographic information (such as your ticket holder status), and/or financial information (such as your credit card number). We also collect information about your location when you use or access our Services via the Mobile App (you may disable the collection and use of your location data through device-level settings).
Site Usage Information: We may receive and store certain types of internet usage information automatically whenever you visit the Website, such as your IP address, browser type, click stream data, Internet Service Provider (ISP), and operating system. See "IP Addresses and Click Stream Data" section below.
Email Communications: When you open emails from us, we may receive a confirmation noting you opened the email, if your computer supports such capabilities. We also may keep track of what emails we send you and what emails you may be receiving from our subsidiaries and affiliates. Additionally, we keep a record of what communications you have opted to receive or not to receive.
HOW INFORMATION MAY BE COLLECTED
We may collect information from you in several different areas on the Services, including but not limited to those described below:
Registration: You may be asked to complete a registration form and provide personal information; you may also be asked to choose a user ID and password in order to take advantage of certain features the Services may choose to offer, such as newsletters or contests. Participation in registration is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to us.
Newsletters and Emails: We offer free newsletters to share information with you about the Services, about us and our affiliates and subsidiaries, or about our marketing partners and advertisers and sponsors. You may receive a newsletter either by registering for a particular newsletter or in conjunction with a special feature or membership for which you have registered on the Services. Participation is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to us. You may also cancel your free email subscription by following the instructions provided in the newsletter or by email at legal@buccaneers.nfl.com.
Promotions, Contests, and Sweepstakes: We periodically operate promotions, contests, and sweepstakes through the Services that may require registration or the submission of personal information. Participation is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to us. Your personal information may be used to contact you for winner notification, prize delivery confirmation or other related purposes, (see the rules of each promotion, contest, or sweepstakes for details about how your personal information will be used). We may also ask your permission to allow us to publicly post your information on the Website, such as on a winner's page, in connection with your participation in a promotion, contest, or sweepstakes. Except as required by applicable law, or with your permission, we will not post your information. We may also share your information with third party vendors involved in the administration of such promotions, contests, and sweepstakes. Please read the official rules carefully before you submit any information.
Surveys or Voting: From time-to-time we may request personal information from you in conjunction with a survey or voting poll. Participation is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to us.
Games: When you register to play games on our Services, you may be asked to provide personal information.
Supplemental Data: We may receive information about you from other sources, including third parties from whom we have purchased data or from our partners, and combine this data with information we already have about you. This helps us to update, expand and analyze our records, identify new customers, and provide products and services that may be of interest to you.
Tracking Technologies: We and our partners use cookies and similar tracking technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users' movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user based as a whole. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website. To manage Flash cookies, please click here: http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html.
Technologies also let us know how many people visit our Website and where visitors go on the site. In addition, technologies can let us know other information, like what web browser is being used to access the website. For registered users, technologies can make using the Website easier for you by saving information such as your passwords or preferences. By tracking how and when you use the Website, technologies help us determine which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the Services are based on data obtained from technologies. Accepting these technologies allows you, among other things to personalize your experience.
We partner with third parties to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third-party partners may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on our Services and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you do not wish this information to be used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking here: http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/. Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.
The Services may feature Nielsen proprietary measurement software, which will allow users to contribute to market research, such as Nielsen TV Ratings. Nielsen believes that you should have a choice about whether to contribute to our research and insights. To opt out of Nielsen measurement, you need only to activate the "Limit Ad Tracking" (for iOS devices) or "Opt out of Ads Personalization" (for Android devices) option in your devices settings. For web, please visit: http://www.nielsen.com/digitalprivacy to learn more about the Nielsen digital measurement products and your choices in regard to them."
IP Addresses and Click-Stream Data: As is true of most websites, we also gather certain information automatically. This information may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), operating system, the files viewed on our site (e.g. HTML pages or graphics), and clickstream data. We use this information for purposes of system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers and sponsors, for example regarding the frequency with which our guests visit various parts of our sites. We may combine this information with personal information. We use click-stream data to help us analyze how visitors arrive at the Website, what type of content is most popular, what type of visitors in the aggregate are interested in particular kinds of content and advertising, and the like.
Transaction Information: If you conduct a financial transaction with our Services, such as the payment of season ticket invoices or the purchase of products, we will ask you to complete an order form that will request certain information from you, including contact information, demographic information and financial information. We will use this information to complete the transaction that you have requested, i.e., to deliver the information, products or other services that you order, and to invoice you. For your protection, such information is collected and stored through encrypted means.
Mobile App: When you download and use our Services, we automatically collect information on the type of device you use, operating system version, and the device identifier (or "UDID"). We also collect your location-based information in order to offer you goods or services based upon your current area. You may opt out of these services or disable the collection and use of your location-based information at any time by editing the settings at the device level.
We use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our Mobile Software on your phone. This software may record information such as how often you use the application, the events that occur within the application, aggregated usage, performance data, and where the application was downloaded from. We do not link the information we store within the analytics software to any personal information you submit within the mobile application.
HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION COLLECTED
As applicable, the information you provide to us may be used to:
contact you about the Website and Services;
contact you relating to your membership status;
send you push notifications in order to update you about any events or promotions that we may be running (if you no longer wish to receive these types of communications, you may turn them off at the device level);
confirm or fulfill an order you have made;
inform you of a prize you have won;
monitor or improve the use of the Services;
customize the advertising and content you see, including through use of location information and geofencing;
monitor compliance with our terms and conditions of use of the Website and Services; and
send you promotional material or special offers on behalf of our marketing partners and/or their respective affiliates and subsidiaries and other third parties.
WITH WHOM THE INFORMATION MAY BE SHARED
At times, we may share your personal information with others for various purposes. The following outlines the ways in which your information may be shared with others and the ways in which you may opt-out of having your information shared:
Third Party Service Providers: We employ other businesses, certain services and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, sending e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for their own purposes, like sending you marketing offers about their products.
Aggregate Information: We may share aggregate information, such as demographics and Website usage statistics, with advertisers, sponsors or other organizations. When this type of information is shared, the other parties do not have access to your personal information.
Other Third Parties and Promotional Offers: We may share your information with third-party business partners, for instance, for the purpose of enhancing our products and services or so they can market their products or services to you. We may also send offers to you on behalf of our marketing partners. When we send you offers on behalf of our partners, we do not give that partner your personal information. If you do not wish to allow us to use your personal information for this purpose, you may use the opt out method detailed in the email sent to you or by contacting us at .
Promotions, Contests, and Sweepstakes:
We may offer promotions, contests, sweepstakes or other activities or offerings that are sponsored or co-sponsored by or presented with identified third parties. By virtue of your participation in such activities or offerings the personal information that you voluntarily submit may be provided to us and the third parties. We take measures to help ensure that our partners protect the confidentiality, integrity, and security of any information we share with them. However, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of our business partners, which may use your information for their own purposes.
Subsidiaries and Affiliates: We share personal information with our parent organizations, subsidiaries and affiliates, and with all members of the NFL Family, including, without limitation, NFL Properties LLC, NFL International LLC, NFL Enterprises LLC, NFL Ventures, L.P. and NFL Ventures, Inc.
Business Transfers: In the event that all or substantially all of our assets are sold or transferred to another party, or another transaction occurs in which your personal information is one of the business assets transferred, all personal information that has been collected and saved may be one of the business assets we transfer. See "Your Acceptance of the privacy policy and notification of changes to the policy" section below.
Administrative or Legal Process: Your personal information may be transferred to third parties without notice to you as required by law, such as to comply with applicable law, , subpoena, or other legal process, to comply with law enforcement agencies, and when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, to protect your safety or the safety of others, to investigate fraud, or to respond to a government request.
LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
You should be aware that when you are on the Services you could be directed to other websites beyond our control. For example, if you "click" on a banner advertisement, the "click" may take you away from our Services to a different website. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors and marketing partners that may use the Website's logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other websites may send their own cookies to you, independently collect data or solicit personal information and may or may not have their own published privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read every website's privacy policy before providing any personal information.
SECURITY
The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once it is received. If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, you may contact us at legal@buccaneers.nfl.com.
We may retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
A SPECIAL NOTE FOR PARENTS CONCERNING PRIVACY
The website and Services are intended for a general audience. We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen on the Services.
The Internet offers children wonderful educational and entertainment resources. Your guidance and involvement are essential to help ensure that children have a safe and rewarding online experience. We encourage you to visit the Direct Marketing Association's Web Website (www.the-dma.org) and explore the Get CyberSavvy! Program as well as the GetNetWise Website (www.getnetwise.org) to learn more about parental control tools.
YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THE PRIVACY POLICY AND NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES TO THE POLICY
By using the Services, you signify your agreement to the terms of our privacy policy. We may amend this privacy policy at any time. If we make a material change to the way in which we collect, use, and/or share your personal information, we will post a notice on our website and / or send an email to users who have provided an email address prior to the change becoming effective. We will assume that you have given your permission for your information to be used under the terms of the new privacy policy, if you do not respond to our email within thirty days or continue to use the Services thirty days after a notice is posted. Please note that you should always update your personal information to provide us with a current email address.Please note that the Services are directed towards users who reside in the United States. By using the Services, you consent to the collection, storage, processing, and transfer of your information in and to the United States, or other countries and territories, pursuant to the laws of the United States. While some of these countries may not offer the same level of privacy protection as your own, we commit to uphold the privacy protections as explained in this Policy.
PERSONAL INFORMATION ACCESS AND CORRECTION
Upon request, we will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. If you would like to make an access request, or if your personal information changes (such as your email address or zip code), or if you no longer desire to access our Services, we will respond to your request and provide a way to correct, update, delete, or remove the personal data you have provided to us. This can be done by using an opt out message in an email, or by emailing us at legal@buccaneers.nfl.com. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.
CALIFORNIA CONSUMER PRIVACY ACT DISCLOSURE Effective Date: December 2019
Last Reviewed: December 2019
To the extent that the California Consumer Privacy Act ("CCPA") is applicable to Buccaneers Team LLC, this California Consumer Privacy Act Disclosure has been drafted to provide additional information to California residents whose personal information is processed by Buccaneers Team LLC.
We generally do not "sell" personal information for purposes of the CCPA. As explained in this privacy policy, whenever you agree to let us collect personal information about you, we will always provide you with an option to prevent this information from being shared for non-administrative purposes with third parties.
The CCPA allows California residents to request that a business that collects consumers' personal information give consumers access, upon a verifiable consumer request, in a portable and (if technically feasible) readily usable form, to the specific pieces and types of personal information that the business has collected about the consumer, the categories of sources for that information, the business or commercial purposes for collecting the information, and the categories of third parties with which the information was shared. California residents also have the right to submit a request for deletion of personal information under certain circumstances, although there may be legal or other reasons that Buccaneers Team LLC must retain your information consistent with California law. If you choose to exercise your CCPA rights, we will not charge you different prices or provide different quality of services unless those differences are related to your personal information or otherwise permitted by law. Please submit your request by emailing legal@buccaneers.nfl.com or calling 1-800 795-BUCS(2827). Please note that your request will not be processed until your identity is confirmed.
QUESTIONS ABOUT THIS PRIVACY POLICY
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or the privacy practices of the Services, contact legal@buccaneers.nfl.com.
Questions regarding this statement should be directed to:
Attn: Website Privacy Policy
Buccaneers Team LLC, One Buccaneer Place, Tampa, FL 33607.
Advertising
Big left arrow icon
Big right arrow icon
Close icon
Copy Url
Three dots icon
Down arrow icon
Email icon
InstagramTwitterFacebookSnapchatShop IconProfile Overlay
AvatarAddAirplayArrow LeftArrow RightArrow UpArrow DownAudioBack 5sBack 10sBack 30sCalendarChartCheckDownLeftRightUpChromecast OffChromecast OnCloseClosed CaptionsBench OffBench OnBroad OffBroad OnVertical OffVertical OnCommentDockDoneDownloadDraftFantasyFilterForward 5sForward 10sForward 30sFull Screen OffFull Screen OnGamepassGamesInsightsKeyLeaveLiveCombineDraftFantasyMenu GamesMenu NetworkMenu NewsMenu PlayoffsMenu Pro BowlMenu ShopMenu StandingsMenu StatsMenu Super BowlMenu TeamsMenu TicketsMenuMore HorizontalMore VerticalMy LocationNetworkNewsPauseplayMultiple PlayersSingle PlayerPlaylistPlayoffsPro BowlPurgeRefreshRemoveReplaySearchSettingsShare AndroidShare Copy URLShare EmailShare FacebookShare InstagramShare iOSShare SnapchatShare TwitterSkip NextSkip PreviousStandingsStarStatsSwapTeamsTicketsVideoVisibility OffVisibility OnVolume HiVolume LowVolume MediumVolume MuteWarningWebsite
Caret downCaret upAt
The browser you are using is no longer supported on this site. It is highly recommended that you use the latest versions of a supported browser in order to receive an optimal viewing experience. The following browsers are supported: Chrome, Edge (v80 and later), Firefox and Safari.
Got it!
